MIKAELA A. WADE

WEB DEVELOPER | DESIGNER

CONTACT



1-317-793-1383



mikaela.wade@gmail.com



Zionsville, IN



linkedin.com/in/mikaela-

TECHNICAL SKILLS

UX/UI Design
Web Development

JavaScript

HTML & CSS

React

NodeJS

PostgreSQL

Bootstrap

Typescript

EDUCATION

ELEVEN FIFTY ACADEMY

Indianapolis, IN

Web Development-JavaScript

APRIL 2020 - JULY 2020

UX/UI Design

JULY 2020 - SEPT 2020

WEBER STATE UNIVERSITY

Ogden, UT

Associate of Applied Science Laboratory Science 2003 - 2005

PROFILE

Exceptionally creative and dependable Web Developer/Designer with a stellar customer service record and superb work ethic. Equipped with entry level programming skills with knowledge in HTML, CSS, and JavaScript languages and experience with React, NodeJS, Bootstrap, and PostgreSQL Database.

WORK EXPERIENCE

SCHEDULING COORDINATOR

Oyler Dentistry, LLC | Zionsville, IN | 2019-2020

Responsible for the coordination of office routines and procedures. Develop and maintain doctor/hygienist schedule to meet practice and financial goals.

- Increase and stimulate new patient growth by supporting promotional programs, to include recall messages, continuing care calls, referral letters, and working with referrals.
- Responsible for answering incoming calls to include, new patient calls, emergencies, scheduling patient appointments, requesting records and follow up. Manage patient communication portal (chat/messaging, email, appointment requests, payments).
- Manage unscheduled list, ASAP list, and treatment pending list, to ensure patient follow through to meet scheduling goals.

MEDICAL ASSISTANT

Allergy and Asthma Care of Indiana I Carmel, IN I 2016-2019 Completed daily tasks in busy allergy and asthma care practice.

- Room patient's and get complete vital signs. Immunotherapy injections, allergy skin testing and spirometry.
- Clinical calls (nurse triage), schedule appointments and pharmacy refills. Management of medical records and documentation.
- Trained to recognize and respond to severe allergic reactions.

MEDICAL LAB TECHNICIAN

Aria Diagnostics I Indianapolis, IN I 2015-2016

Urine drug toxicology screenings for a start up lab company.

- Checked in and logged each sample.
- Prepped samples using manual dilutions.

MIKAELA A. WADE

WEB DEVELOPER | DESIGNER

CONTACT



1-317-793-1383



mikaela.wade@gmail.com



Zionsville, IN



linkedin.com/in/mikaela-

COMPETENCIES

CERTIFICATES

LEAN SIX SIGMA YELLOW BELT

Indianapolis, IN 2015

VOLUNTEER

FUNDRAISER VOLUNTEER
Bosma Enterprises - Dining in
the Dark
Indianapolis, IN
2014-2019

WORK EXPERIENCE CONTINUED...

MEDICAL LAB TECHNICIAN

Mid America Clinical Labs I Indianapolis, IN I 2014-2015 Assist hospital physicians in the diagnosis and treatment of illnesses and medical conditions by providing clinical testing and specimen analysis on blood, urine, and body fluid samples.

- Conduct lab tests in the areas of hematology, coagulation, urinalysis, chemistry, blood banking, and microbiology.
- Calibrate, operate, and maintain all instrumentation and equipment.
- Document all required quality controls, quality improvement, and preventative maintenance.
- Record and report results accurately utilizing appropriate mechanism.

MEDICAL LAB TECHNICIAN

ARUP Laboratories I Salt Lake City, UT I 2006-2008

Provided services of both technical and non-technical nature in the

Huntsman Cancer Hospital by performing selected waived, moderate, and highly complex analytical testing.

- Conduct lab tests in hematology, chemistry, coagulation, urinalysis and minimal blood banking.
- Prepared specimens for precessing in the laboratory.
- Performance and documentation of quality control and equipment maintenance.

PROJECTS - https://github.com/mikwad22

STATIC WEB PAGE- https://mikwad22.github.io/StaticLayout/ Recreated a website using HTML & CSS. Deployed to GitHub. Eleven Fifty Academy I Indianapolis, IN I MAY 2020

GHIBLI API- http://apichallenge2020-7b97e.web.app

A Website that uses fetch to pull data from an open API to generate content for application. Built with HTML, CSS and Bootstrap. Deployed to GitHub.

Eleven Fifty Academy I Indianapolis, IN I MAY 2020

MOOD TRACKER APP- https://moodtrackerapp.herokuapp.com/
Full Stack application using PostgreSQL, Express, React and Node. Styled with Reactstrap and CSS. Allows user to Sign-up, Login, Post or Log Mood, Edit, and Delete. Deployed to Heroku.

Eleven Fifty Academy I Indianapolis, IN I JUNE 2020